{"data":[{"question":"They are going to have to leave soon, and so do we.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"to have to","c":"leave soon","d":"so do","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- So do-> so are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"How much times did Rich and Jennifer have to do the experiment.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"How much","b":"did Rich and Jennifer","c":"have to","d":"do","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- much-> many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"She refused ''to tell us why was she crying''.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"refused","b":"to tell","c":"us","d":"was she crying","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Was she crying-> she was crying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"A lunch of soup and sandwiches do not appeal to all of the students.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"of soup","c":"do not","d":"appeal to all of","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Do not-> does not","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs. Stevens, along with her cousins from Mexico, are planning to attend the festivities.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"with her cousins","b":"from","c":"are","d":"to attend","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Are->is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"All students are looking forward to spend their free time relaxing in the sun this summer.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"students","b":"are","c":"to spend","d":"in the sun","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Spend-> spending","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"He knows to repair the carburetor without talking the whole car apart.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"knows","b":"carburetor","c":"talking","d":"apart","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n-Talking-> taking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"A five thousands dollars reward was offered for the capture of the escaped criminals.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"five thousands dollars","b":"was offered","c":"the","d":"of","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Five thousands dollars-> five thousand dollars","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"Give the package to whomever has authority to sign for it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"whomever","b":"has","c":"to sign","d":"it","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Whomever-> whoever","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"},{"question":"In the relatively short history of industrial developing in the United States, New York City has played a vital role.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"relatively","b":"developing","c":"in","d":"has played","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Developing-> development","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"33","type":"1"}]}